grandprix.com 2007-02-02

# GrandPrix.com - Privacy Policy

The Motorsport Company, the developer of the GRANDPRIX.COM website, recognize that many Internet users are concerned about privacy. Accordingly, we have developed this notice to explain our online information practices, identify the kinds of information we collect, and describe how we may use this information. 

I. Gathering and Use of Information 

The Motorsport Company collects only the following information from its users: anonymous use information, and personally identifiable information. 

Anonymous use information may be automatically collected by some of our websites and services as you and others browse the web pages or utilize the services. Such information may include the identity of your internet service provider and its approximate geographic location, the operating system of your computer, the type of web browser you are using, the identity of the website that referred you to our website or services, the time and date that you access the website or services, and the webpages or content that you view. This information may be aggregated and utilized to analyze web traffic and usage or to improve the design and content of our websites and services. 

Personally identifiable information, by contrast, is only collected by The Motorsport Company if you voluntarily submit them to us, for example, make a purchase from the website. At present, such information includes your contact information, financial information, username and password, zip code, gender, and age. We use this information to contact you, execute orders, collect payments, to respond to your requests and inquiries concerning our products and services, to notify you of updates and news, to personalize your browsing experience and to generate anonymous aggregated demographic information. In addition, we encourage, but do not require, you to provide us with information about your interests and hobbies so that we can forward messages and materials to you that we believe you will enjoy. 

II. Cookies 

The Motorsport Company’s websites and services may utilize a standard Internet technology known as cookies, which are small data files that your browser stores on your computer to record your preferences and to remember the information you have accessed or provided in the past. Cookies do not contain personal information about you unless you have voluntarily provided it to us as described above. Most web browsers allow you to disable cookies if you do not wish to receive them. 

III. Security Measures 

The Motorsport Company utilizes reasonable and appropriate measures to safeguard any personal information that you provide to us. However, since no transmission or storage of electronic data is ever completely secure, we cannot warrant or guarantee that your information will never be released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy. 

IV. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties 

The Motorsport Company does not disclose any user information other than in the following ways: 

The Motorsport Company provides statistics related to website traffic, aggregated customer demographics, and related information to third parties, such as advertisers. This information is not traceable to individual users of our service. 

The Motorsport Company may share personally identifiable information with our partners, agents and contractors in connection with the provision of specific services to users. We require that these parties not use any such information for any purpose other that the provision of these services, and require them to comply with our privacy and security practices. 

The Motorsport Company reserves the right to disclose any user information when we believe that doing so is required by law or necessary to protect the property, rights, or safety of ourselves, visitors to our websites, or other persons, or in the context of a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, where there is a pledge of confidentiality from the receiving party. 

V. Privacy of Children Under the Age of Thirteen 

The Motorsport Company is committed to protecting the safety and privacy of children. The Motorsport Company does not permit the registration or purchasing of materials from the website by children known to be under the age of 13. The Motorsport Company may collect online contact information from a child only for the purpose of responding directly on a one-time basis to a specific request from the child, or where otherwise permitted by law. In such case, The Motorsport Company will not use the collected information for any other purpose. 

VI. Privacy Policy of Third Party Websites and Content Providers 

Some webpages and services may contain content provided by and links to websites operated by third parties. This Privacy Policy does not extend to such third party content or websites, and The Motorsport Company makes no warranty or representation concerning the privacy practices of such third parties. 

VII. Updates to the Privacy Policy 

We may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and such modification shall be effective immediately upon posting on this webpage. Such posting will constitute notice to you of the revised policy. Therefore, you agree to review this page periodically, and your continued access or use of the The Motorsport Company website or services shall be deemed your acceptance of any modifications. 

VIII. Contact Information 

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at: 

Privacy Coordinator  
The Motorsport Company  
75 Oak Street  
Suite 101  
Norwood, NJ 07648  
privacy@grandprix.com
